<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Practice App</string>

    <string name="ikigai">The Ikigai book introduces you to various topics related to the art of living, such as the blue zones, longevity, logotherapy, flow, yoga, tai chi, and resilience. It defines what Ikigai is and its rules. The book says that living a long and full life is under your control to an extent. Your habits and life choices can make a significant difference from an early age. The authors of this book conducted 100 interviews in Ogimi, Okinawa (the world’s longest-living community) to gain an in-depth understanding of the longevity secrets of centenarians and supercentenarians. Each chapter delivers a well-researched account of Okinawans’ lifestyle, attitude, mindset, diet, and routine. The authors argue that your Ikigai keeps your body fighting and living longer. </string>

    <string name="algorithms_to_live_by">Brian Christian and Tom Griffiths have done a terrific job with Algorithms to Live By. This book merges computer science with everyday life, which makes it a fun introductory read for those, who don’t really know how computers work, yet a cool way to learn how to live better, even if you’re very experienced in computer science. An algorithm is really nothing more than a recipe: a series of steps you can follow to solve a very specific problem, that can be re-run as often as you like and will always provide a solution. Our brains use them all the time to approximate incomplete information or focus on just the essential facts at hand and thus allow us to make a decision without being paralyzed.
    Here are 3 scenarios in particular, where you can deliberately use algorithms to make your life easier:

    1. Clean up your home using sorting algorithms.
    2. Limit the time you spend on time management with a few simple to-do list patterns.
    3. Use game theory and mechanism design to improve how you make decisions.
    </string>

    <string name="atomic_habits">When it comes to habits, James suggests that environment is the invisible hand that shapes human behavior. That’s why a prompt is always the first step in performing any habit. It may not always be external, but, most of the time, it will be. There are several popular methodologies that try to predict how and why we do what we do, such as Charles Duhigg’s habit loop, Gretchen Rubins four tendencies, or BJ Fogg’s Tiny Habits behavior model. James offers a more refined version of what Duhigg described in The Power of Habit and while all of these approaches are different, none of them are mutually exclusive. From the four-step pattern he suggests, James then derives four laws of behavior change, which correspond to one part of the loop each. You can apply these to all kinds of good habits, like running, working on a side project, spending more time with family, and so on. Conversely, do the opposite for bad habits. Make them invisible, unattractive, difficult, and unsatisfying. For example, you could hide your cigarettes, add financial penalties, get rid of all lighters, and only allow yourself to smoke outside in the cold.
    </string>

    <string name="our_mathematical_universe">The story goes as follows. Our observable universe is the result of an explosion, the big bang, some 13.7bn years ago. The explosion, now called inflation, is a solution to Einstein\'s theory of gravity in which a subatomic blob of non-diluting substance (dark matter might have this property) can double its size at regular time intervals while keeping its density constant. After inflation ends the expansion of space slows to roughly the present rate, gravity having coalesced matter into the familiar stars and planets we observe in space. The inflation solution explains many puzzles but includes a shocker: the process doesn\'t terminate – inflation is eternal. This means that just as our universe inflated and coalesced an infinite number of others, remote from us in space and time (but in principle accessible), were doing the same. And since, in an infinite space "everything that can happen according to the laws of physics does happen", some of these would contain planets and inhabitants virtually indistinguishable from ours. The assemblage of all these "Level 1 parallel universes" containing our observable universe is called the multiverse – that is, the Level 1 multiverse.
    </string>

    <string name="outliers">To debunk the myth of the “self-made man”, which might be the most popular myth of our time, Gladwell first looked at how much your skills really influence where you end up in life. Of course practice matters, and so do genetic predispositions in sports, but there are limits to their influence. As it turns out, once you cross a certain threshold with your skills and abilities, any extra won’t do you much good. For example, since the 1980s, the average height of an NBA basketball player has been 6′ 7″. Even if you grow to be 7′ tall, those additional inches won’t give you a huge advantage over other players. Gladwell also looked at law school students and their performance. Some law schools lower their admission requirements for racial minorities, and even though these students tend to perform worse than their non-minority peers both before and in law school, this gap completely disappears once they graduate. They make the same valuable contributions, get paid just as much and receive as many honors as their peers. Why? Because once you’ve reached a certain level of legal expertise, other factors start to take over and influence your career, like social skills, how good your network is, and even catching a lucky break.
    </string>

    <string name="sapiens">Homo sapiens had some distinct advantages that let them get ahead of other human species on earth. Most importantly are the differences in humans brains. These began with the Cognitive Revolution around 70,000 years ago. This was a time when mental development rose relatively suddenly, setting our ancient ancestors apart. With their newfound better brains, Homo sapiens could outperform other species of humans. Forming communities, developing better hunting tools, and building simple trade networks made everything about life and survival easier. As the ability to communicate grew, so did the population. Language set our species apart from others because it made us able to distribute information more freely. This helped early people share lessons about predators and food with each other. Because humans could cooperate as a society and flexibly, ideas spread which made even more progress possible. Not long later, the Agricultural Revolution gave humans another great advantage. By deserting old hunting and gathering methods for farming, mankind further improved their situation. This new method, although slow to begin, was far more efficient than the old ways, and let population growth explode. Things were looking up but there was a problem. Coping with this larger community would require mankind to make even more advances to get to where we are today.
    </string>

    <string name="the_intelligent_investor"> Often also called value investing, intelligent investing according to Benjamin Graham rests on 3 principles. An intelligent investor always analyzes the long-term evolution and management principles of a company before investing. They always protect themselves from losses by diversifying investments. Intelligent investors never look for crazy profits, but focus on safe and steady returns. A famous quote by Warren Buffet is about his 2 rules for investing. Rule No. 1: Never lose money. Rule No. 2: Never forget Rule No. 1. That’s exactly what intelligent investing is. Nobody can predict the next Facebook, but everyone can protect themselves against losses. By doing a thorough analysis, intelligent investors find stocks with a gap between their current price and the intrinsic value the company holds and will eventually unlock. This is based on the evidence collected from looking at the company’s history and their management values. The intelligent investor invests in a few of those companies, in order to not lose everything when things go wrong and then sits back, being perfectly happy with collecting 10%, 12% or even 15% a year in returns.
    </string>

    <string name="tiny_habits">I love setting goals and building new habits. For the last 15 years, I’ve set my goals at the beginning of the year. But many times I found myself failing to uphold all of the massive changes I was trying to make. It was hard to understand why. I knew that exercising, sleeping, and reading more were all good for me, but I still couldn’t follow through! As I eventually found out, I fell for the Information-Action Fallacy: We assume knowing facts will be enough to make us change. The truth is that no matter how much data we have, and no matter how well it motivates us to begin, it’s just never enough to keep us going. In the author’s experience, there are three drivers of behavioral change: Epiphanies, Environmental Changes, Tiny Adjustments to Existing Habits. An epiphany is a sudden revelation, and, like facts, they’re not enough to inspire us in the long-term. The big problem with these is that we can’t control when they come to us. Environmental changes, like getting your friends to come to the gym with you, are also just as uncontrollable. That’s why tiny habits are so important because we can change them and, if done right, they do last. When you begin small, even so much that it seems strange to you, the change becomes sustainable over the long-term. And when you increase your ability to be consistent, you dramatically improve your chances of success.
    </string>
</resources>